<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!-- Nyingma -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_NYINGMA">
			<Text>Nyingma</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_NYINGMA_PEDIA">
			<Text>The Nyingma school, meaning "Ancient Ones," is the oldest of the four major schools of Tibetan Buddhism. It traces its origins to the first dissemination of Buddhism in Tibet during the 8th century, particularly through the Indian master Padmasambhava (Guru Rinpoche) who is revered as the "Second Buddha" by Nyingma practitioners. The school is characterized by its transmission of Dzogchen (Great Perfection) teachings, considered the highest and most definitive path to enlightenment.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Nyingma teachings are organized into nine vehicles (yanas), with the highest three being the Inner Tantras unique to their tradition. The school maintains both monastic institutions and a strong tradition of lay tantric practitioners (ngakpas). Their canon includes not only the standard Buddhist scriptures but also a vast collection of terma (treasure texts) - teachings said to have been hidden by Padmasambhava and discovered by subsequent masters when the time was ripe for their revelation.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Karma Kagyu -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_KARMA_KAGYU">
			<Text>Karma Kagyu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_KARMA_KAGYU_PEDIA">
			<Text>The Karma Kagyu is the largest sub-school of the Kagyu tradition, one of the four major schools of Tibetan Buddhism. Founded by the First Karmapa, Düsum Khyenpa (1110-1193), it is headed by the Karmapa, the oldest tulku (reincarnate lama) lineage in Tibetan Buddhism, predating the Dalai Lama lineage by nearly three centuries. The school is renowned for its emphasis on meditation practice and the direct transmission of realization from master to student.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Karma Kagyu tradition is particularly known for its teachings on Mahamudra (Great Seal), a method of direct insight into the nature of mind. The school has produced many renowned meditation masters and yogis, and maintains the tradition of the three-year, three-month retreat for intensive meditation training. The Black Crown ceremony, performed by the Karmapa, is considered one of the most sacred rituals in Tibetan Buddhism, said to liberate those who witness it through sight alone.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Drikung Kagyu -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_DRIKUNG_KAGYU">
			<Text>Drikung Kagyu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_DRIKUNG_KAGYU_PEDIA">
			<Text>The Drikung Kagyu lineage was founded by Kyobpa Jigten Sumgön (1143-1217), a disciple of Phagmo Drupa. The school takes its name from Drigung Thil Monastery, established in 1179 in the Drikung valley of central Tibet. The Drikung Kagyu is renowned for its profound teachings on the Six Yogas of Naropa and particularly for its mastery of the practice of Phowa, the transference of consciousness at the time of death.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The lineage is known for maintaining one of the most complete sets of Kagyu teachings and for its emphasis on retreat practice. The Drikung Kagyu developed a unique system of philosophical study integrated with meditation practice. The school is also famous for its sky burial site at Drigung Thil, considered one of the most sacred in Tibet. The tradition continues under the leadership of two heads: the Drikung Kyabgon Chetsang and the Drikung Kyabgon Chungtsang.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Drukpa Kagyu -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_DRUKPA_KAGYU">
			<Text>Drukpa Kagyu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_DRUKPA_KAGYU_PEDIA">
			<Text>The Drukpa Kagyu, or "Dragon" lineage, was founded by Tsangpa Gyare Yeshe Dorje (1161-1211), who established the first Drukpa monastery after witnessing nine dragons (druk in Tibetan) ascending to heaven at the site. The school became the state religion of Bhutan, which is called Druk Yul (Land of the Dragon) in reference to this lineage. The tradition is known for its unconventional teaching methods and the "crazy wisdom" of its masters.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Drukpa lineage has produced many renowned yogis, including Drukpa Kunley, the "Divine Madman," whose unconventional methods and humor are legendary throughout the Himalayas. The school emphasizes the equal importance of study, contemplation, and meditation, along with the practice of the Six Yogas of Naropa. The Drukpa Kagyu maintains strong traditions of both monasticism and lay practice, with particular emphasis on pilgrimage and retreat in remote locations.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Sakya -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_SAKYA">
			<Text>Sakya</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_SAKYA_PEDIA">
			<Text>The Sakya school, meaning "Grey Earth" after the color of the soil at its main monastery, was founded in 1073 by Khön Könchok Gyelpo. The tradition rose to political prominence in the 13th century when Sakya Pandita and his nephew Chögyal Phagpa became spiritual advisors to the Mongol rulers, with the Sakya lamas serving as regents of Tibet under Mongol patronage. The school is renowned for its scholarly tradition and systematic approach to Buddhist philosophy and practice.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Sakya tradition's main teaching is the Lamdre (Path and Result), a comprehensive system that integrates sutra and tantra teachings. The school is known for its emphasis on scholarly learning, maintaining that intellectual understanding must accompany meditation practice. The Sakya lineage is unique in having a hereditary leadership, passed down through the Khön family. The tradition has produced many great scholars, including Sakya Pandita, Gorampa, and Rendawa, who was one of Tsongkhapa's main teachers.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Gelug -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_GELUG">
			<Text>Gelug</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_GELUG_PEDIA">
			<Text>The Gelug school, meaning "Virtuous Tradition," was founded by Je Tsongkhapa Lobsang Drakpa (1357-1419), who initiated a reform movement emphasizing monastic discipline, scholastic study, and graduated stages of meditation. The tradition became the most politically powerful school in Tibet when the Fifth Dalai Lama assumed temporal authority in the 17th century. The Gelug is now the most widespread school of Tibetan Buddhism, largely due to the international recognition of the 14th Dalai Lama.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Gelug tradition is characterized by its emphasis on the study of logic and debate as tools for understanding emptiness, and its systematic presentation of the stages of the path (lamrim) to enlightenment. The school maintains large monastic universities that were among the largest educational institutions in the world, including Ganden, Drepung, and Sera. The Gelug synthesized the best of earlier traditions while emphasizing ethical discipline as the foundation for tantric practice. The tradition is headed by the Ganden Tripa, while the Dalai Lamas and Panchen Lamas are its most recognized figures.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Jonang -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_JONANG">
			<Text>Jonang</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_JONANG_PEDIA">
			<Text>The Jonang tradition was founded by Kunpang Tukje Tsondru (1243-1313) and takes its name from the Jomonang valley in central Tibet. The school is distinguished by its philosophical view of zhentong (other-emptiness), which differs from the rangtong (self-emptiness) view predominant in other schools. The tradition is particularly renowned for its preservation and practice of the Kalachakra (Wheel of Time) Tantra, including its unique six-branch yoga practice.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Despite facing near extinction in the 17th century when the Fifth Dalai Lama converted Jonang monasteries to Gelug institutions due to political and philosophical conflicts, the tradition survived in remote areas of eastern Tibet. The Jonang school was officially recognized again as a distinct tradition only in the late 20th century. The lineage is known for its profound meditation practices, particularly the Kalachakra completion stage practices, and its unique philosophical contributions to the understanding of ultimate reality. Master Dolpopa Sherab Gyaltsen and Taranatha are among its most influential scholars.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Bon -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_BON">
			<Text>Bon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_BON_PEDIA">
			<Text>Bon is Tibet's indigenous spiritual tradition, predating the arrival of Buddhism in the 7th century. According to Bon sources, the tradition was founded by Tonpa Shenrab Miwoche thousands of years ago in the land of Olmo Lungring. While maintaining distinct practices and deities, Bon developed in dialogue with Buddhism over centuries, adopting similar monastic structures and philosophical systems while preserving unique shamanic and ritualistic elements.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Modern Bon, sometimes called "Yungdrung Bon" (Eternal Bon), presents a complete system of Buddhist-style teachings including sutra, tantra, and dzogchen, while maintaining distinctive practices such as circumambulating sacred sites counter-clockwise and unique iconography. The tradition emphasizes the importance of the natural elements and includes practices for harmonizing with environmental forces. Bon has been recognized by the Dalai Lama as Tibet's fifth religious school and maintains important monasteries including Menri and Yungdrung Ling. The tradition offers an alternative historical narrative of Tibet's spiritual development and preserves many ancient Tibetan cultural practices.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Kadampa -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_KADAMPA">
			<Text>Kadampa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_KADAMPA_PEDIA">
			<Text>The Kadampa school was founded by Dromtön (1004-1064), the foremost Tibetan disciple of the great Indian master Atisha Dipankara (982-1054). Atisha was invited to Tibet to help restore pure Buddhist practice after a period of decline, and his teachings emphasized the integration of sutra and tantra within a framework of ethical discipline. The Kadampa tradition is known for its practical, down-to-earth approach to spiritual practice and its emphasis on guru devotion.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Though the original Kadampa school ceased to exist as an independent tradition, having been absorbed into what became the Gelug school founded by Tsongkhapa (who studied extensively with Kadampa masters), its teachings remain foundational to Tibetan Buddhism. The Kadampa emphasis on lamrim (stages of the path), lojong (mind training), and the integration of compassion and wisdom influenced all later schools. The tradition's key texts, including Atisha's "Lamp for the Path to Enlightenment," continue to be studied throughout Tibetan Buddhism. The Kadampa approach represents the successful synthesis of Indian Buddhist learning with Tibetan cultural forms.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>
